internetinfluences.com 2016-05-02

# Privacy Policy | Internet Influences

We are committed to protecting our visitors and staff privacy with online services that respect their privacy. This page summarizes the privacy policy and practices for our web site. Our site does not automatically gather any personal information from you, such as your name, phone number, or e-mail address. This information is only obtained if you provide it voluntarily, through contacting us via our online form.

Any personal information you do provide is only obtained at the point of collection.

## Information collected automatically via the Internet

Some of the information collected does not identify who you are. Other information, such as your location, may identify you depending on the naming standards followed by your Internet service provider. You may wish to ask them about their policies and practices.

While we make no attempt to link the information captured to the identity of individuals, the information captured may identify the following:

  1. The Internet domain and location from which you access our web site;
  2. The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;
  3. Screen resolution of your monitor;
  4. The date and time you access our site;
  5. The pages you visit; and
  6. If you linked to our web site from another web site, the address of that web site.

This information is used to help us make our site more useful to our audiences by learning about the number of visitors to our site, and by monitoring traffic patterns and the types of technology our visitors use. We do not track or record information about specific individuals and their visits.

Visitor information is not disclosed to anyone except our personnel who need the information for legitimate business purposes such as responding to a request.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of text information that is sent to your browser when you access a web site. Your browser will return this cookie information to the domain where the cookie originated. While we do not regularly use “cookies” to track how our visitors use the site, when cookies are used, they may be used to help you fill in forms or track your use of the sites. The length of time that the cookie will reside on your machine will depend upon the specific set-up of the particular sites you visit.

If you are concerned about the use of cookies, you can refer to the help information in your browser software for information on how to disable cookies. If you wish to delete cookies from your machine, consult your browser’s help files for instructions on how to do so.

## Privacy and Links to Other Sites

Our web site may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the content and the privacy practices of other web sites and encourage you to examine each site’s privacy policy and disclaimers and make your own decisions regarding the accuracy, reliability, and correctness of material and information found.

## Information Collected in Web Forms

If you should choose to provide us with personal information – by filling out a form and submitting it to us through our website- we will use that information to respond to your message and to help us get the information you have requested. We do not collect personal information for commercial marketing or distribution to any private organizations.
